<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Product on Chengsheng&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Product on Chengsheng&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Launching Questions in Product Sense </title>
      <link>/post/launching-questions-in-product-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/launching-questions-in-product-sense/</guid>
      <description>Launching Question  Launching products is one of the most important duties of a PM, so it makes sense that interviewers would ask how you would do this. 
Approach   The Product: Discuss the vision of the product, along with its strengths, weaknesses, and risks. What does the product ultimately hope to achieve? What is its target market? What are the things that would worry you? Who is it competing against and how is it positioned against those?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Questions in Product Case</title>
      <link>/post/marketing-questions-in-product-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/marketing-questions-in-product-case/</guid>
      <description>Marketing questions are about product positioning, customers, and handling competition.  
Approach:  Understand the Company: What are the company’s goals? What is its mission? What are its strengths and weaknesses? What threatens it? 
 Understand the Competition: Break down the competition into segments. Who competes and in what market?(竞争对手是谁) How do they position themselves? How entrenched are they?(怎么巩固自己的位置) What are their strengths and weaknesses? 
 Understand the Customers: Who are your customers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Questions in Product Case </title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>Boston Street | Shot on iPhone X
 Type of Metrics (Acquisition, Activation, Retention, Referral, and Revenue) 
User acquisition (用户注册率） How many users do you have ?  How and why has user base grown overtime?  How many active users are there? How do we define what an active user is ?  Where are users coming from? Are they referring their friends?  Which channels are the most effective in getting users</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>